<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title></title>
    <link>/bios/</link>
    <description>Recent content on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2021 Lonesome Still
</copyright><atom:link href="/bios/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Garrett Massman</title>
      <link>/bios/gm/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/bios/gm/</guid>
      <description>Garrett Massman got his start on electric guitar but was eventually corrupted by his bluegrass roots in Signal Mountain, TN. He brings a twang to his songwriting, guitar, dobro, mandolin, programming code, and software documentation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ian Kelmartin</title>
      <link>/bios/ik/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/bios/ik/</guid>
      <description>Ian comes to the Bay by way of Humboldt County, CA, hailing originally from PA. Versed on Bass and Guitar, his songs are inspired by good beer, nature, and fish - after all, if he stuck to his day job he&amp;rsquo;d clam up! While the band shares musical leadership, Ian is known as the heart of the band, bringing everyone together.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Michelle Yu</title>
      <link>/bios/michelle/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/bios/michelle/</guid>
      <description>Michelle Yu is a California native who has been playing violin before even the band can remember! A converted classical musician, the fiddle provides a natural outlet for her day job saving lives. She can be found strumming some old time tunes, clogging away at an Old Time Fest&#39;, or corralling friends into a country line dance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nat Hendel</title>
      <link>/bios/nh/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/bios/nh/</guid>
      <description>Nat Hendel is a true local, coming out of Walnut Creek, CA. Picking up mandolin before it was cool to have a pandemic hobby, Nat is know for his &amp;ldquo;mandolines&amp;rdquo;, that is a mix of badass playing with clever songwriting lyrics.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
